

# CONTACT

khunzinshine@gmail.com

+959 788926700

**Q** Yangon, Myanmar

# **EDUCATION**

## **University of Computer Studies**

Bachelor of Computer Science Completed in 2020

# **SKILL**

- HTML5/CSS3
- Javascript/ Typescript
- Sass/Scss
- TailwindCSS
- Bootstrap
- React
- Next
- Redux/Redux Toolkit
- Node
- MongoDB
- Agile Development

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Sep 2020 | Udemy

The Agile Sumurai Bootcamp

Feb 2021 | Udemy

**React - The Complete Guide** 

Feb 2021 | Code with Mosh

**Mastering React** 

Apr 2022 | Udemy

The Complete Nodejs Developer

# Khun Zin Shine

# Frontend Developer

#### **PROFILE**

Enthuse in design | develop and problem solving. Strong knowledge in Javascript, ReactJS, React Native, NextJS and NodeJS. I've been 3+ years in software development at the digital banking/financial and retail groceries industry. I'm willing to new challenges and cutting-edge technologies.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Full Stack Developer**

Jan 2023 - Present

City Holdings Limited

- Design and implement City Rewards mobile wallet.
- Develop Admin dashboard to manage application function.
- Realize and fix to improve application performance and scalability.
- Develop new features to enhance the user experiences.
- Design and implement complex systems that work seamlessly.
- Optimize the database structure.

# **Frontend Developer**

Mar 2021 - Dec 2022

# AYA Bank (AYA Innovation Labs)

- Developed web admin portal for AYA Pay mobile wallet functionality management.
- Developed reporting portal and corporated financial portals with the requirements from business team.
- Developed the web view static pages that were integrated in AYA Pay
- Built the reusable components, user-friendly and reactive web apps.
- Realized and fixed unnecessary components rendering to improve application performance.
- Implemented function components using react hooks, custom hooks and HOC components.
- Optimized application performance such as React.memo, Lazy Loading, useCallback and useMemo.

#### **Quality Assurance Tester**

Mar 2020 - Feb 2021

#### AYA Bank (AYA Innovation Labs)

- Wrote unit testing using Mocha (Javascript Framework).
- Tested manual testing to AYA Pay mobile wallet, Web Admin portals, Merchant portal and corporated financial portals.
- Executed test cases under varying circumstances.
- Dynamic billers testing that were integrated in AYA Pay mobile wallet.
- · Tested Web Automation Testing using Katalon Studio.
- Wrote test cases in deep functionality and deadline-driven.

# Web Developer (Internship)

May 2019 - July 2019

Acroquest Myanmar Technology Co., Ltd

- Developed Web Application using Angular and Java (Spring Boot).
- Took the notes in deadline-driven and project time management.